

DAVID VAUGHAN

Atlanta, GA

323-483-1571

David.Vaughan86@gmail.com

LINKS O

- https://github.com/davidvaughan86
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/david-j-von/
- davethedev.org

PROJECTS

"Dining with the ISS"

https://github.com/davidvaughan86/dining-with-the-ISS https://spacestationlunchbreak.com

Dining with the International Space Station is my first group project. We combined two different public API's to design this amazing orbital tracker will inform the user of the exact location of the ISS and provide great places to eat near(under) it. The station moves quickly so click quickly, search, and get a move on because the station waits for no one.

"DigitalCrafts Quiz App"

https://github.com/davidvaughan86/DigitalCraftsQuizApphttps://digitalcraftsquizzes.com

My team and I created an App called "DigitalCrafts Quiz App" using Express and Node.JS to assist students with their knowledge in coding. We found that playing helpful study games and practice quizzes helped us understand coding even better, so we wanted to create an App where users can practice these techniques. By using DigitalCraft Quiz App, students will be prepared for future coding projects and interviews! We used PostgresSQL and Sequelize to store quiz questions and answers as well as user sessions and log in.

"Credit Sharks"

https://github.com/davidvaughan86/CreditSharks-Capstone

I was asked to create an online shop by the CEO of "Credit Sharks LLC". This prototype showcases my abilities in React to create E-Shops. This application uses JavaScript, React, and CSS. I used Material UI and StripeJS. This was a solo project, and the goal is to create a fully functional online store with Stripe API. The app features product display, email to merchant contact, and checkout.

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I love thinking of applications and websites that would be useful in my downtime. I often find myself looking at websites and writing code to improve the look of the website. I enjoy creating new mobile applications based off other's ideas many might find useful for their everyday lives. Professionally I have been a leader for over 8 of my 14 years of work experience. My work ethic is top notch, and my excellence is even higher. Personally, I'm a big nerd when it comes to comics and history and have tons of random facts from both categories. I can provide value in any capacity and

have proven such with my education and work experience detailed below.

SKILLS

- React
- Redux
- JavaScript
- HTML5
- CSS
- Python

- Local Area Technologies
- Information Security
- Scrum
- Agile Workflow
- Project Management
- Git

EDUCATION

Certification | Software Development

DigitalCrafts LLC, Atlanta, GA

Some College | Information Technology Security And Defense

American Military University, Charles Town, WV

CERTIFICATIONS
WORK HISTORY

• Full Stack Development, DigitalCrafts LLC - 10/20-2/21

DEVELOPER IN RESIDENCE

03/2021 to CURRENT

DigitalCrafts LLC| Atlanta, GA

- I assist in teaching the Full-stack Immersive Course for people who want to change their careers and become software developers!
- I love writing code and creating new projects and programs while helping others do the same.
- Creating beautiful webpages and building mobile applications is a passion of mine while also learning new languages.

ACCOUNT MANAGER

05/2019 to 03/2021

AT&T | Atlanta, GA

- Worked directly with consumer and enterprise to provide technical assistance and knowledge on mobile devices, device application, and network issues.
- Worked closely with many CRM and POS applications and collaborated on new ideas that could be developed and implemented to help improve revenue.

RETAIL STORE MANAGER

09/2010 to 01/2019

T-mobile USA | Atlanta, GA

- Supported professional development of team members up to and including manager level by implementing best practices and skills training and providing mentoring.
- Assisted with technical aspects of Mobile devices both software and hardware.

02/2021